# **MACKENZIE THOMAS**

Front-End Web Developer

Web: mackenziethomasdevelopment.github.io

Email: mackenzie.thomas54@gmail.com

Phone: 620-755-1547

Address: 1602 West 9th Street Apt. 2, Lawrence, KS 66044

Front-End Web Developer with 3+ years of experience and an Associates Degree in Web Development and Digital Media. Proficiency in HTML, CSS,

and JavaScript. Creative, self - starter with excellent problem solving skills and capable to take on a leadership role. I have a strong desire to continue learning.

## **EDUCATION**

2015-2017 + Web Development and Digital Media

Johnson County Community College

Associate's Degree

2012-2014 + Video Game Development and Animation

2012-2014 + Video Game Development and Animation
Hutchinson Comminity College

Associates's Degree

## **SKILLS**



### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2016 - Present + Senior Tutor of Web Technologies

#### Johnson County Community College

Taking complicated technical concepts and simplifying them to make it easier for others to understand, demonstrating patience, demonstrating leadership ability.

2017 + Freelance - www.bensonpsyc.com

#### Web Designer and Developer

bensonpsyc.com is a website I worked on with Dr. Richard Benson from Overland Park KS. He is a psycholgist who helps childen, teens, and adults with a wide range of emotional and behavioral concerns. I am using Wordpress to develop the website.

2016 - 2017 + Freelance - www.bellezdesignstudios.com

#### Web Designer and Developer

I listened to my client's expectations and needs and created a website that with Wordpress that addressed those expectations and needs.

2014-2016 + Sales Associate

#### RadioShack

Responsible for listening to customer needs and being capable of solving problems on my own and in a group environment. Responsible for organizing large amount of products.

## REFERENCES

Available on request